We can't control...
who we fall in love with or when it happens.
It's more about...
how you handle it.
Are you hiding something from me?
You need to make up your mind.
But holding on to him like this...
will only cause him more pain.
Can we go back to be friends?
Of all the things you have,
am I the easiest one to let go of?
Come here, let's dance.
Come on.
Are you tired?
Yeah, I've never danced like this before.
That's cap.
For real.
Have you really never come here to dance?
This is my first time and I ran into you.
It must be destiny.
Do kids from CPA always talk so cringe?
Hey, come on.
Well, can I dance with you next time?
It's up to you.
This is a park, not my backyard.
"I want to you come with me."
You can say it like this.
I want to you come with me.
I'm out.
Are you flustered?
I'm going to hit on you.
[Grade 9, second semester]
How can I solve it?
I can't figure it out.
Fuse.
What are you doing?
The math homework that due today.
It's so difficult.
Oh.
Didn't you copy your friend's?
Nah.
I couldn't finish copying.
They already submitted their homework.
I don't even know how to solve it.
Chill out. Let me see.
Oh.
You need to solve this problem
the way teacher taught us last week.
Well, I'll do it for you.
Really?
Thanks.
Have you submitted your homework yet?
Not yet.
Hey.
But you have to submit it today.
It's the last day.
Otherwise, you have to run five laps around the field.
I forgot to bring my homework notebook.
Well, you don't have to do it anymore.
Why?
I can do it for you.
I'm sure I'll get everything right.
You don't have to.
If everyone has already submitted their homework,
who will run with you?
I'll run with you.
Um.
Canteen auntie give me this.
Drink up.
Then we'll run together.
Are you serious?
Um.
We're friends, how could I abandoned you?
Thanks.
So refreshing.
Oh.
Excuse me.
It's okay.
I guess I'm not breaking up with Jeen after all.
Can we go back to be friends?
Hey, do we have math test today?
Tee, can give me a glance during the test?
Hey.
Just turn toward me then.
Fuse.
What's up, bro?
I brought UNO today, wanna play?
Fine.
Let's go then.
Come on.
Let's play.
Don't tell me...
I'm not a villian.
What's going on?
You seem unusually cheerful.
I've been working out lately.
I'm telling you, if you worked out,
you would feel so good.
Count me in then.
Me too.
Wait, you can't.
If you want to work out, go different parks.
-Why?
Actually,
I have...
lower back sprain.
Let's help him.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Ouch.
What are you looking for, Frame?
I'm already full.
But is there anything else to eat?
Like what?
Dessert.
Finish your food, we have to head to class soon.
I was just thinking about studying.
You? Studying?
I want to read and take notes in the book.
An actual book.
Hurry and finish your lunch.
That's cool.
Tee.
Your collar.
Thanks.
Fuse.
Will you eat a fried egg?
It he didn't want to eat it,
why would he order it?
Teacher.
Yes?
May I borrow class rep for a moment?
Uh...
Um, sure.
Did you actually bring class rep?
Hey, did my friend mess with you?
I'm sorry.
Are you kidding?
He didn't mess with me.
Are you two close?
Since when?
Nosy.
Frame, talk nicely.
Okay.
Est, move over.
No, this seat already has its owner.
Wit, move over.
Nah, I can't get up.
What the heck?
Come here.
Sit down.
Take a seat.
Est, can you move over a bit?
So cool.
His girlfriend is calling again.
Morning call, afternoon call.
Do you guys stay on the line all night too?
All night, my ass.
Hello?
Hi, Fuse. Remember when I told you
I have a volleyball test today?
Yeah, I remember.
My arms hurt so bad and I even failed the test.
Oh.
I have to buy something this afternoon.
Can you give me a hand?
Um, sure.
Yay! It's nice to have a boyfriend.
I'll give you a call after school.
Keep going on your study.
Keep going on your study, baby.
Speak for yourself, Est.
What's wrong?
I haven't seen you eat anything.
I'm just feeling down.
You can talk to us if anything is wrong.
Right.
Yeah.
Thanks a lot.
Let's go.
Go, go.
Fuse, are you gonna eat a fried egg?
You can have it.
Thanks.
Mama.
Yes?
What's happening?
There is a handsome guy
walked in with a bouquet of flowers.
He brought it for someone but I don't know who.
Congrats on your win yesterday.
Is it for me?
Yes, thanks for helping our school win yesterday.
Gosh!
Thank you.
Well.... are you single?
You seem so calm normally,
so I thought you were a quiet person.
But you were so cool yesterday.
If you're single, can I be your boyfriend?
You need to make up your mind...
before things get any worse.
But holding on to him like this...
will only cause him more pain.
Someone reported that…
this is your pic.
Is it true?
Don't tell me he touched you.
[So, did Tee take the bouquet?]
[How am I supposed to know? I sat next to you.]
[Est, do you know? @Est]
[I don't know.]
[But I know.]
[How did you know?]
[I asked guys from class 13.]
[I'm telling you, the tea is good.]
[Send 1 if you want to know.]
[Fuse unsent a message.]
Oh.
What?
You want to know?
Yeah.
Come closer.
I won't...
tell you.
One point.
Wit. Tell me.
I won't.
Tell me.
Wit.
If you want to know, ask him yourself.
[Will you go this afternoon?]
[Yeah.]
[I'll go too.]
[Why did you tell me?]
[Just go if you want.]
Lookmo.
Let's go.
Where to?
A library.
Huh?
You planned to work on the project with me.
No, I mean...
I'm tied up right now.
I have a plan with him.
Oh.
With Yok?
Working out together again?
Mo.
Let's be honest.
Are you serious about this person?
I'm serious.
This one will be the mother of my children.
Whoa.
That's sick, blond guy.
Congrats, dude.
For being a teen dad.
But this afternoon,
you have to work on the project with me.
Since it's due tomorrow.
[You can dance first.]
[I'll join you for that song later.]
[Don't dance with anyone else.]
[I'll wait.]
See you.
Hey, let's go.
Hurry up.
Let me see your chat.
Give me.
Later.
I love you, baby.
Later, later.
Hey.
It's nothing.
Fuse, let him go.
I won't tell you.
Let's go, Wit.
WIt, wait for me.
Oh.
Why don't you go with your friends?
Aren't we friends?
Yeah, I...
Where there is Frame, there is Est.
Just one day, please.
You can leave first or I'll kick you.
I'd be heartbroken without you.
Hey, I'm serious. I'll punch you unless you go.
I'm leaving.
Fine.
Hold on, let me gather my things.
Go.
Okay, I'm out.
I'm leaving.
Book, let's go.
I'll hold it for you.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Remember, if he ask you anything,
don't admit it.
Just say that someone impersonate you.
Okay?
Book.
I'll wait for you here.
You know why you're here, right?
Someone reported that this is your pic. Is it true?
No, it's not.
Then why did your shirt appear in the picture?
Are you gonna say you were impersonated?
How will you prove it?
Even though I'm a student teacher,
it's my duty to take care of students.
If you are impersonated, I must tell other teachers...
to take you to file a police report.
Is that how you want?
If you don't want me to tell anyone,
you have to let me prove it myself.
How should I prove it?
Should we start with...
Your tattoo right here.
[I know who you are.]
[The whole school is probably curious who BKBOii is.]
What the hell are you doing?
You're a teacher.
Who invited you?
You're still asking?
Why did you call my friend here?
Did you bring your man to wait?
Great, both of you will be
sent to the school discipline office.
And you, one more trip to
the discipline office and you're probably expelled.
Me?
If I'm expelled, you won't even pass the training.
How could I not pass?
I should even be praised.
Since I monitor student behavior.
Do you even know that your man
posts risque pics for others to see?
When I saw his pics,
I couldn't believe Narongsak could do that.
Why hide it when he can show it off?
Between my man posting his pics...
and a teacher asking for those pics from student,
which one do you think has a harsher punishment?
What did you say?
You're a teacher of an audiovisual room.
Don't you know that...
camera...
can record video?
And you really think I only set up one camera?
Stay away from my man.
And keep this to yourself.
Otherwise,...
you'll be infamous.
Did all that studying…
make you forget what today is?
Shall we do something to celebrate our anniversary?
Are you okay?
Did he do anything to you?
Don't tell me he touched you.
I'm here.
I promise I'll never let this happen again.
You're good.
No worries.
Do you think he'll actually report it to the discipline office?
If he want to get in trouble as well, let him report it.
It can't be like that.
I don't want you to be expelled.
Me?
It must be him.
I have evidence videos.
If nothing happens,
I won't watch the videos.
And I'll delete them too.
Thank you.
Did you fold more paper cranes?
You like them?
I believe them.
There is a legend.
If a person fold 1,000 paper cranes,
then that person gets to make one wish.
Really? What would you wish for?
Alright.
It's late now.
I'd better go.
Oh.
Or do you want me to stay?
Nope.
If anything happens, call me anytime.
I'm always available for you.
Frame.
Huh?
Thank you for everything.
How can you be this cute?
My heart is mealting right now.
Then don't leave yet.
Huh?
For real?
You can stay here as long as you want.
You sure? How many hours can I stay?
Forever.
Will you go out with...
Hey!
Book.
I have to be the one who say it.
Why?
Well...
Uh...
I mean...
I've never asked for anything from anyone in my life.
You are the only one that I ask for.
Stay with me.
Will you be my boyfriend?
Okay.
I gave you my heart.
And I'm not taking it back.
How cringe.
I'm cringe but still your boyfriend.
I'm not going back.
I want to try somthing as your boyfriend.
Frame, stop it.
I'm going to send to class rep three rounds.
I mean three assignments.
Frame.
Can I get it in return?
Another side too.
I have something to tell you.
I can't hold it anymore.
Frame.
What are you talking about?
Oh, this one is good but a bit high in sugar.
Or should I buy this one instead?
Fuse.
Oh.
You should buy this one.
You alright? You look lost in thought.
Are you studying a lot?
A little bit.
Did all that studying...
make you forget what today is?
What day is it?
It's our anniversary.
We've been dating for a year now.
Hey, I do remember.
I thought you meant something else.
What would you like to eat?
It's on me.
Um.
I would like to have a cake.
Which shop?
I don't want to eat at the shop.
Where is your parents?
They are out of town right now.
What about your brother?
He's also out of town.
No one is home?
Should we go to the shop instead?
It's not appropriate.
Who will know?
There is no one here.
You're overthinking.
What's wrong with just bringing my boyfriend home?
You sure?
Let's have some cake.
Have a seat.
Hey.
Just a try.
Try this.
Is it tasty?
I want to try it too.
Huh?
That's enough.
Well... I'll be right back.
Fuse.
I brought you some water.
Jeen, why are you dressing like this?
Well, it's hot.
Fuse, can you take off my necklace?
I'm afraid it'll get cake on it.
Why don't you turn around?
This position is fine.
Hurry up.
Shall we do something to celebrate our anniversary?
Tonight...
Let's stay together until the morning.
That's Tea, my brother.
I forgot that she has a brother.
They look nothing alike.
Oh.
No, Fuse. I can explain.
It's not what you think.
Fuse.
I invited him along.
He's at the same tutoring place with Book.
What are you mad at?
I should be the one who is mad
since you didn't come yesterday.
What's wrong with you?
You...
You tell me first.
You first, mine is not that big deal.
But yours is probably a big deal, right?
Damn. That's so wild.
Are you sure that you didn't get it wrong?
Yeah, she hasn't texted me yet.
That's so weird.
How can I tell which one is real?
Where is he?
Ouch.
Est!
Hey.
Let's go.
Or we won't make it in time.
What was that?
Hey.
Ouch.
What?
So what?
I did some digging.
His name is France.
Not Tea.
He is our age.
And he definitely has no siblings.
Wow, Est.
You...
You're so nosy.
Come on.
I knew it.
When I saw them myself,
they're sitting so close as if were glued together.
My friends also told me that...
he hooks up with people nearly every school.
This guy texts all beautiful girls.
So, this means Jeen got played too.
Ugh.
Do you still care about her?
Whoa.
How could he do such things?
Right.
Listen up.
Whatever she does to you,
she'll get it back the same way.
Take it easy.
Smile.
Great.
Hey, guys.
I want to play that one.
Okay, let's play.
Come on.
Hey, count me in.
Hold on.
Wait for me.
Hey, Lookmo.
What brings you here?
Playing arcade games.
Well... why didn't you dance with me yesterday?
Right...
there was a new song yesterday.
Too bad you missed it.
It's fine.
Let's dance together next time.
What's wrong?
If you don't feel like talking, I'm out of here.
Yesterday...
who did you dance with?
Yesterday?
Never mind.
I don't want to bother you anymore.
Whoa.
You're good at defense.
Hey, Fuse.
Hey.
What brings you here?
Est called me.
What about you?
I'm here to pick up him after tutoring class.
Right?
Did you get any scores?
Hey, I did.
Did you score some goals, Fuse?
I didn't.
I've already exchanged it.
I invited him along.
He's at the same tutoring place with Book.
Tee, you should play it.
You must score some goals.
That's easy.
Go ahead, dude.
Nice strike.
Why don't you play it, Frame?
I bought you a beverage. It's good.
How much is it?
It's fine.
Well, I'll treat you some snacks later.
Great.
Wanna play?
Of course.
Do you know how to play? I"ll teach you.
I don't know, teach me.
This couple too?
I have no idea.
Aren't you close to Tee?
I really have no idea.
Fuse.
Frame.
Let him sleep.
He told me he didn't get any sleep last night.
(Frame) Shall we leave now?
(Book) It's up to you.
(Frame) What should I do?
(Frame) Do you want to go back now?
(Book) You decide. I'm fine with going back.
Hey, I'm leaving. I have to take Book home.
I'll go with you. My mom told me to go home.
Me too. Let's go.
-Okay, you guys can leave.
-See you.
I'll look after Fuse.
-Bye.
-See you.
See you.
Let's go.
Come on.
Which way? Turn right?
Lookmo, can I talk to you for a minute?
Tee, can you look after him for me?
I'll be back soon.
What's your problem?
Why are you making that face?
What are you mad at?
I should be the one who is mad
since you didn't come yesterday.
Why are you mad?
You already had company.
Since you didn't come,
so I brought a friend to dance instead.
Are you sure he's just friends?
Kris.
That's a badass name.
That is my friend, Kristina.
Hi, darling.
Are you over it yet?
I also wanted to dance with you...
but you couldn't come.
That's all I want to say.
I'm off.
Hold on.
Wanna grab some food?
My treat. Let me make it up to you.
And...
I want to have dinner with you as well.
Hello? Lookmo?
He's still sleeping.
You want me to take him home?
What about you?
Ah.
I'll take him home instead.
Okay.
Lookmo told me to take Fuse home.
So we have to wait until he wakes up then.
If I fell asleep like Fuse, would you look after me?
Of course, we're friends.
So, am I just a freind to you?
Is there still any hope for me?
Sys.
Don't put your hope in me.
It's not that you're not good,
but I'm just not ready to be with anyone.
I'm sorry.
Are you not ready?
Or do you already have someone in your mind?
Even though he keeps hurting you,
you still don't think about walking away?
Love is nonsense.
I'd better go.
Get home safely.
Oh!
Aren't you dating with Sys?
He's a friend.
I thought you like him at first.
Don't say like that.
As if you don't know who I like.
You told me to get over you.
But it's not that easy.
Because I'm not you.
If you still can't get over me,…
(Fuse) Can we…
(Tee) How's Jeen doing?
About Jeen...
Never mind.
I don't want to know it anymore.
About what we talked, I'm going to make it.
I told you.
I can do everything for you.
Tee, hear me out.
I mean...
Let's go. I'll take you home.
X, O, X.
You have to hand in it to teacher.
Really?
Yeah.
It's okay. It's just a back cover.
Hello, class rep.
Do you really have to
bow to him every morning and afternoon?
Well, I respect him.
If you don't have a love life, just hang in there.
Why did you say it harshly?
Move over a bit.
Ugh.
When will I can start studying?
Alright.
Look at this.
The answer of this question is in this paragraph.
But the answer of my heart is here.
I'm sick of this smell. Go away.
This smell?
Wit, you good?
Smell of love.
Is there anything smelly?
Did you say those words?
Yeah.
So cringe.
Did I say something wrong?
Nothing is wrong.
Hello?
I'm at school now.
Did you bring your shirt?
Shall we go dance this afternoon?
Hello.
Hey, I'm still talking.
Yes, baby.
Est.
Hey.
Give it to me.
What's going on?
Hello?
See you this afternoon. Bye.
Oh.
Tee.
Champ and Copter.
How are you doing?
I told you I'm not you because I love you.
Between Tee and you,
I don't know what's going on.
But if you can only see him as a friend,
you should step back.
Tee.
Please don't get over me yet.
Can I have a little more time?
And I'll never break your heart again.